 <odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="illuminations_types_of_meditation" name="Type Of Meditation"> 
    <section class="eachsection section-topbtm-padding">

        <div class="mycontainer">
            <div class="section-typo-inner" style="max-width: 100%;">
                <span class="blakwordtexts ">Types of </span>
                <h2 class="">Meditation </h2>

            </div>
            <div class="row typeofmeditation">
                <div class="col-xl-4 col-lg-4 col-md-6 col-sm-6 col-12 typeofmeditation-item">
                    <img src="/ppts_website_theme/static/src/img/typeofmeditation1.svg" />
                    <h5>Mindfulness Meditation</h5>
                    <p>These meditations involve focused attention and awareness on the present moment, by observing
                        your natural breath and thought patterns until we are able to move beyond the mind into a place
                        of stillness and silence.</p>
                </div>
                <div class="col-xl-4 col-lg-4 col-md-6 col-sm-6 col-12 typeofmeditation-item">
                    <img src="/ppts_website_theme/static/src/img/typeofmeditation2.svg" />
                    <h5>Movement Meditation</h5>
                    <p> These meditations involve incorporating an activity such as walking or a hobby such as painting
                        or dancing through focused concentration where we move into a space of total oneness with our
                        activity and away from the world of multitasking, in order to channel our creativity, intuition
                        and stillness. </p>
                </div>
                <div class="col-xl-4 col-lg-4 col-md-6 col-sm-6 col-12 typeofmeditation-item">
                    <img src="/ppts_website_theme/static/src/img/typeofmeditation3.svg" />
                    <h5>Spiritual &amp; Energy Based Mediation</h5>
                    <p> These meditations involve establishing a deeper spiritual connection with what we may call the
                        universe, divine, higher self in order increase our faith, by moving beyond our mental control
                        into a space of trust, faith and intuition. </p>
                </div>
                <div class="col-xl-4 col-lg-4 col-md-6 col-sm-6 col-12 typeofmeditation-item">
                    <img src="/ppts_website_theme/static/src/img/typeofmeditation4.svg" />
                    <h5>Sound, Vibration &amp; Mantra Meditation</h5>
                    <p> These meditations involve continuous repetition and chanting of high-energy sounds, vibrations
                        and mantras, which increase our energy vibration, bring us into a space of peace &amp; tranquility &amp;
                        awaken the wisdom and compassion within us. </p>
                </div>
                <div class="col-xl-4 col-lg-4 col-md-6 col-sm-6 col-12 typeofmeditation-item">
                    <img src="/ppts_website_theme/static/src/img/typeofmeditation5.svg" />
                    <h5>Visualization &amp; Guided Meditation</h5>
                    <p> These meditations take you through a beautiful healing journey by guiding your mind and body
                        into a state of deep relaxation through visualization. In this tranquil state, positive
                        reinforcement within the subconscious mind will accelerate the powerful manifestation process of
                        our thoughts into creating an empowering reality. </p>
                </div>
                <div class="col-xl-4 col-lg-4 col-md-6 col-sm-6 col-12 typeofmeditation-item">
                    <img src="/ppts_website_theme/static/src/img/typeofmeditation6.svg" />
                    <h5>Full Moon Meditation</h5>
                    <p> Full moons are about completion, change, releasing and cleansing. Meditating at the time of a
                        full moon offers a powerful healing opportunity supporting you to release blocked energies and
                        limiting beliefs. This powerful guided meditation manifests your dreams and deepest desires,
                        allowing you to come into alignment with your higher self and connect with the endless
                        possibilities the Universe can provide for you.
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>

    </section>
        
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>
